<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>newt@noslogan</title><link>https://noslogan.org/</link><description>Recent content on newt@noslogan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noslogan.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pita Bread</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/pita/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/pita/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is transcribed from &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MzNv-MjLc-w">Max Malkiel&amp;rsquo;s Recipe on Youtube&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It makes 8 fluffy pitas. I generally don&amp;rsquo;t use the kitchen oven for these because the pizza oven makes great pitas. You can also use a pizza stone in a regular oven if you give it plenty of time to heat up.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Christmas Raised Pie</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/vegetarian-christmas-raised-pie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/vegetarian-christmas-raised-pie/</guid><description>&lt;p>I wanted to use a hot water crust pastry to make a Christmas main course. Given that we don&amp;rsquo;t eat meat, raised pork pies weren&amp;rsquo;t going to work. I&amp;rsquo;ve made a Christmas pie before that used butter beans, cheese, garlic and herbs so I decided to work from that and a raised pork pie and create a new recipe.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Kayaking in Florida</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/florida/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:45:13 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/florida/</guid><description>&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;ve been on Florida on holiday (vacation?) with Em&amp;rsquo;s dad and his wife. We visited the theme parks, they were OK. Disney is much more mellow than Universal; there are some great rides at both but Owen and I (the ride fans) like roller coaster rich environments best really.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We also went to the Kennedy Space Center. It&amp;rsquo;s been thirty something years since I was last there and I was a bit bemused to find it has become theme parked.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How much yeast?</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/yeast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/yeast/</guid><description>&lt;p>I always forget how much of each different type of yeast to use. An aide memoire…&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sourdough Muffins</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/muffins/</guid><description>&lt;p>This makes about 20-24 muffins. They are best when you eat them absolutely fresh. Just make sure they are cooked &lt;em>enough&lt;/em>. They aren&amp;rsquo;t like the one you buy in the supermarket - they&amp;rsquo;re a bit more dense. You can cook them until they start to brown.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sourdough Pancakes</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/pancakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/pancakes/</guid><description>&lt;p>This always feels like cheating because there&amp;rsquo;s baking soda and powder as well as sourdough but it makes really tasty pancakes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chocolate Pecan Chunk Cookies</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/chocolate-chunk-cookies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/chocolate-chunk-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>This recipe is so easy. I think I originally got it from a cookbook that I ordered from Carnation. The condensed milk makes the cookies softer. You can use almost any nuts. I&amp;rsquo;ve used pecans, hazelnuts, almonds and walnuts in the past.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Setting up zsh</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/tech/zsh/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/tech/zsh/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="note-to-self">Note to self&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Setting up zsh consistently. Assuming zsh is installed…&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pavlova</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/pavlova/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 09:15:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/recipes/pavlova/</guid><description>&lt;p>I love pavlova. There seem to be &lt;em>so&lt;/em> many different recipe variations for the meringue. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried loads but I always come back to this one. My mum gave this one to me about twenty years ago. This recipe has never let me down. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried ones from cookbooks and the meringue just hasn&amp;rsquo;t worked as well. This works.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The raspberry and passion fruit is our addition; you can use any fruit you like.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My coding environment</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/tech/programming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 16:25:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/tech/programming/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about the things that I use to do my job. There&amp;rsquo;s the obvious things like a web browser (I &lt;em>like&lt;/em> Safari but I &lt;em>use&lt;/em> Chrome). A lot has changed since because I&amp;rsquo;ve gone from a job where writing code was most of my job at MarkLogic to a job where writing code is something that I might do in order to get something in my job done (at Redis).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Local Walks</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/walks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 13:07:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/walks/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just some pictures from recent local walks&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Battersea Brown</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/battersea-brown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/bread/battersea-brown/</guid><description>&lt;p>A long time ago in a city not so far away (Battersea), there was the Lighthouse
Bakery. We bought bread there. In particular we loved their &lt;strong>Battersea Brown&lt;/strong>
wholemeal bread. We moved to Sussex and there was sadness because we couldn&amp;rsquo;t buy
the bread anymore. I mentioned this to the lovely people who ran the bakery.
Clearly, we weren&amp;rsquo;t the first because they had a printed copy of the recipe and
method ready to hand over.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Broad-bodied Chaser</title><link>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/broad-bodied-chaser/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/posts/photos/broad-bodied-chaser/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was helping my son mow my neighbour&amp;rsquo;s garden yesterday when something flew past me. My first thought was “that was a &lt;em>huge&lt;/em> wasp” but I didn&amp;rsquo;t see it well. Then I saw movement and realised it was a dragonfly. I&amp;rsquo;m rather fond of dragonflies. This lovely creature let me take photos of her (I &lt;em>think&lt;/em> it&amp;rsquo;s a female but it could be an immature male). &lt;a href="https://british-dragonflies.org.uk/species/broad-bodied-chaser/">She&amp;rsquo;s a broad-bodied chaser&lt;/a>. I imagine that she hatched from our neighbour&amp;rsquo;s pond.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://noslogan.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noslogan.org/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>My name is Nic Gibson and I am a geek. This is, in general, a good thing&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These days I work for &lt;a href="https://redis.io">Redis&lt;/a> as a Senior Technical Account Manager – that is, I try to ensure that Redis customers are happy Redis customers and stay that way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I spent the twenty odd years before that doing things that involved XML, initially in publishing and then (working for MarkLogic) in financial services.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>